[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 8 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "43",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "43",
        "44",
        "42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 6 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "58",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "59",
        "58",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "8",
        "7",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 6 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "17",
        "15",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "3",
        "5",
        "2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "5",
        "4",
        "3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 4 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "0",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 9 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "46",
        "47",
        "45",
        "48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 10 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "91",
      "options": [
        "91",
        "92",
        "90",
        "93"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 5 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "50",
      "options": [
        "51",
        "52",
        "49",
        "50"
      ]
    }
]